# Kacper Walęga

Fullstack Developer



+48 512 012 757 kacper.walega21@gmail.com

# Personal profile

I am a **Fullstack Developer** with experience in **Django (Python)** and **Next.js/React.js**. I am passionate about creating fast, accessible applications that delight users and meet their needs. Named Time magazine's Person of the Year in 2006.

## Website & socials

<u>LinkedIn</u>

**GitHub** 

## **Skills**

React.js/Next.js/Redux

TypeScript/Node.js

CSS/SCSS/Material UI

Django/Python

Docker/GitHub

**REST API/SQL/POSTGRES** 

Agile/SEO

## Languages

English

C1

Spanish

Beginner

# Work experience

#### **Fullstack Developer**

#### **FXMAG**

Jan 2024 - Aug 2024 Kraków - remote

In my position, I was responsible for creating innovative features such as **currency calculators** and **stock market quotations**. My duties included **retrieving data from external sources**, **storing it in our databases**, and implementing the **full frontend for both desktop and mobile versions**.

#### **Frontend Developer**

#### **NOKIA**

Oct 2022 - Dec 2023 Wrocław - remote

I was responsible for developing new features for an internal tool supporting managers. My duties included **creating advanced reports** on test automation, presented in the form of **interactive tables** with **filtering capabilities** for large data sets and **generating charts**.

## **Python Developer Intern**

# NOKIA

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022

Wrocław

I was responsible for creating **efficient backend views** for generating reports on test automation. My tasks included **extracting data from databases** and providing **optimal views** for analyzing and **presenting detailed reports**.

# **Education**

#### Master's Degree

**Wroclaw University of Economics and Business** 

Oct 2023 - Present

Wrocław

**Business Informatics** 

### **Bachelor's Degree in Engineering**

Wroclaw University of Science and Technology

Oct 2019 - Jan 2023

Wrocław

Systems Engineering

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purposes necessary for the recruitment process, as well as for future recruitment processes, in accordance with the Act of May 10, 2018 on the Protection of Personal Data (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in accordance with the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (GDPR).